Wynn Mo

Website wynnmo.com

Phone 027 486 4378 E-mail wynnmo.micro@hotmail.com

I am a final year Computer Systems Engineering student at the University of Auckland, driven by my passion for coding, design, and crafting exceptional user experiences. My goal is to combine my technical skills in coding and systems engineering with my love for human-centered design principles to create innovative solutions.

Education

Feb 2020 - 2024

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours): Computer Systems Engineering

University of Auckland

Related courses: Software Architecture, Al and Machine Learning, Object Oriented Programming, Data Structures and Algorithms, Computer Systems Design, Design Software Practice, Software Development Methodologies, Hardware Software Systems

Skills

Programming: React, Javascript, Java, C, Python, VHDL, Git version control

User Experience: Responsive design, Functional UX design, Wireframing (Figma), User flow

Consulting: solution architecture, sales, pricing strategy, product demonstration, customer needs analysis

Experience

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

Digital Consulting Intern

Beca. Auckland

- Designed and developed Long-Term Project (LTP) tracker app for city councils using Microsoft PowerApps and Dataverse.
- Leveraged PowerBI to display statistical data and generate insight for the LTP tracker app.
- Delivered live app demos to New Zealand city councils and provided consulting services for contract negotiations.

Jan 2016 - Dec 2019

Driving Range Attendant

Russley Golf Club, Christchurch

 Collected driving range balls and general greenkeeping - picked up pins, collected carts, collected sand buckets, swept golf storage room, and introduced new club members.

Projects

Pikatune

React/Javascript

A Pokémon-themed game that serves as a playlist generator, allowing players to create Spotify playlists based on their favorite Pokémon types. Players can engage in quiz-based gym battles to est their playlist knowledge, earn experience points, level up, add friends, and customize their playlists.

Body Pawsitive

Raspberry Pi Pico, React/Typescript

A smart scale system implemented from scratch with hardware and circuit design, to weigh and log the weights of dogs, all managed through a web application.

Many more at wynnmo.com

Leadership / Volunteering / Extracurriculars

Jan 2023 - Present

Vice President

Robogals Auckland

- Collaborated with a team of volunteers to design and deliver engaging robotics workshops for young women in primary and secondary schools, fostering their interest and empowerment in STEM fields.
- Managed a team of 108 active volunteers, with 60 of them dedicating their time and efforts to multiple workshops.
- Conducted 44 workshops at 23 different locations, with 70% of the workshops being conducted at long-distance locations.

Jan 2023 - Present

Events Manager

Rainbow Engineering

- Plan, coordinate, and execute a wide range of events and activities aimed at promoting diversity and inclusion in the field of engineering.
- Collaborate with team members and external partners to conceptualize events such as panel discussions, networking events, and social gatherings.

Jan 2022 - Dec 2022

Partnerships and Sponsorships Manager

Robogals Auckland

- · Increased sponsorship numbers from 4 to 11 since 2021, by reaching out and liaising with STEM/Engineering companies
- · Organized collaborative workshops and events with sponsors such as EY, Xero, Beca, and Counties Energy

Accomplishments

2019 NCEA Art Design Scholarship worth \$500

2017, 2018, 2019 1st place in Inter-school Christchurch Chess Competition

2018 Competed in New Zealand Chess nationals, placing 4th

2016 Awarded grade 8 Piano ABRSM certificate, the highest practical graded music exam

References

References available upon request